Kourtney Boston

Account Manager

Contact

Address

Austin, TX, 78734

Phone

5129101046

E-mail

bostonkourtney@gmail.com

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/kourtneyboston

Skills

Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)

Account Management

Teamwork

Problem Solving

JavaScript

Real Estate Transactions

Residential Real Estate

National accounts

Strategic planning

Coordinating documents

Salesforce expertise

Account servicing skills

Systems and software

Dynamic and Passionate individual with multiple years of sales and customer service experience in-person and virtually. Client focused and Profit motivated with strong Communication, Problem Solving, and Teamwork skills. Educated in Retail Operations and Marketing with a deep passion for Real Estate and Technology. Currently finishing the University of Texas Austin Full Stack Web Development certificate program. New to coding but excited to continue learning and growing!

Work History

2020-02 -Current

Account Manager REX

REX, Austin, TX

- Manage a client load 50% higher than 80% of Account Managers nationally while maintaining top tier NPS scores and consistently ranking among the top 3 Account Managers in Revenue Generation company-wide
- Establish relationships and generate excitement about REX with existing clients in a fast-paced and highly disruptive environment
- Provide exceptional support to current and former sellers and buyers by anticipating their needs, monitoring home sale activity and ensuring marketing is performing optimally
- Serve as company liaison with all parties involved in the sales transaction as a licensed real estate agent in multiple states
- Manage projects to get home listings live on both REX's website and alternative platforms in multiple states with multiple teams concurrently.
- Pitched brand products to customers, highlighted benefits and redirected objections to secure more than \$546k in sales in 2021.

2018-05 -2020-01

Real Estate Agent

HomePlace, Austin, TX

- Generate leads via inbound calls, online advertising & social media -Produce sales/leasing monthly revenue of \$5K+
- Maintain detailed records of customer and operational data

programs

Relationship building and management

Territory Management

Prioritizing workflows

Client rapport

Account management

Business Development

CRM Systems

- Identify client needs, clarify information, & researched customer data
- Regular B2B meetings to establish and grow working relationships and accomplish team goals
- Developed and maintained relationships with clients through networking, postcards and cold calling.

2017-10 -2020-01

Human Resources Specialist

FEMA, Kansas City, MO

- Coordinate interviews, fingerprinting, and background investigation procedures with regional and national security teams
- Held high risk public trust security clearance while utilizing and maintaining federal funds systems to check and transfer funds to disaster accounts
- Researched and developed guideline material for best financial practices while on disaster travel
- Liaised between management and employees to deliver conflict resolution, alleviate problems and interpret compensation and benefits policies.
- Reviewed existing policies and procedures to make recommendations for enhancing work productivity, recruitment, hiring processes and talent management.
- Maximized team knowledge and productivity by training, monitoring and directing employees in application of best practices and regulatory protocols.
- Used Concur and National Travel systems to identify cost-effective travel accommodations for clients.

Education

2011-01 -2015-01

Bachelor of Science: Fashion and Retail Management

The Art Institutes of Austin - Austin, TX
I was educated in the marketing, retail operation,
sales, events, managerial aspects of fashion. I also
learned the essentials of the creative, procedural, and
technical aspects.

2006-08 -2010-06

High School Diploma

Cedar Park High School - Cedar Park, TX

Certificates & Licenses

- Concur Government Edition Local FATA Issuing authority - FEMA
- Integrated Financial Management Information System (IFMIS)
 Issuing authority - FEMA
- Real Estate Salesperson
 Issuing authority Nevada Real Estate Division
 Credential ID S.0190459
- Texas Real Estate Salesperson License
 Issuing authority Texas Real Estate Commission
 Credential ID S.704683